Guide to the Smith Family Papers
Yale University Divinity School Library
- Printed/Professional Material, Series III
  - Foochow Messenger (selected issues), 1910-1940 (Box 13, Folder 49B)
  - Miscellaneous pamphlets re. mission work in China (Box 13, Folder 49C)
  - Banyan Echo, 1937-1938 (Box 13, Folder 49)
  - Reprints, articles, n.d. (Box 13, Folder 50-51)
  - Tape Recordings of HHS (Box 13, Folder 52)
  - Chinese Language Materials: pamphlets (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Chinese Language Material: Student Directories and By-laws, Ing-Tai High School and Elementary School, 1913-1937 (Box 15, Folder 54-55)
  - Chinese Language Material: Foochow Union Seminary commencement program and classbook (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Chinese Language Material: Calling cards, invitations, envelopes, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Chinese Language Material: church material, compositions, corres., n.d. (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - Chinese Language Material: ABCFM Annual Report, maps, block print, etc., n.d. (Box 15, Folder 59)
  - Chinese Language Material: 2 war posters, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 60)
  - Chinese Language Material: Catalogue of a store in Peking, n.d. (Box 15, Folder 61)
- Photographs, Series IV
  Box 16 contains single and mounted photographs, while photograph albums are contained in box 17 and 18.
  - Smith family, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 1)
  - Groups, misc., n.d. (Box 16, Folder 2)
  - Re: World Council of Churches Assembly, New Delhi, India; a few early photos (Box 16, Folder 3)
  - Chinese Christian religious art, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 4)
  - Mounted photos in small red case, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 5)
  - Mounted photos in large red case, n.d. (Box 16, Folder 6)
  - Albums, n.d. (Box 17, Folder 7-10)
  - Album/Scrapbook: "Inghok District of Foochow Mission, China.", n.d. (Box 17, Folder 11)
  - Album - HHS- Family and Wenshan Girls School, 1936-1941 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - 6 photographs, n.d. (Box OV1)
  - 2 leaves of a photo album, c. 1906 (Box OV2)
- Personal Items and Memorabilia, Series V
  - Cloth Materials and Embroidery
    - 8 banners--commemorating birthdays, anniversaries, etc., n.d. (Box OV1)
    - 3 flags, n.d. (Box OV1)
    - 5 small items, n.d. (Box OV1)
  - Papers and Documents
    - 10 scrolls, n.d. (Box OV1)
    - 1 watercolor, "The White Pagoda," by Mrs. William Strong, n.d. (Box OV1)
    - 1 poster, "60 Anniversary of our Mother School", 1961 (Box OV1)
    - 1 elementary school poster (Box OV1)
    - 1 "First Draft of Ingtai City Church...", 1914 (Box OV1)
    - 1 student register (Box OV1)
    - 1 map and calendar of Sundays (Box OV1)
    - 1 Congregational school catalogue--course listings, 1926 (Box OV1)
    - 1 Rights of Ownership and Property document from the U.S. Consulate, Foochow, China, 1938 (Box OV1)
    - Honorary degree presented to HHS by Defiance College, 1963 (Box 18, Folder 5)